<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>startrek on miker.org</title>
    <link>https://miker.org/tags/startrek/</link>
    <description>Recent content in startrek on miker.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:28:49 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miker.org/tags/startrek/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Premiere Movie Script Library</title>
      <link>https://miker.org/premiere-movie-script-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Mar 2021 13:28:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miker.org/premiere-movie-script-library/</guid>
      <description>While I was looking for a nice reading copy of Raiders of the Lost Ark I discovered an old series of screenplays called the Premiere Movie Script Library. The defunct Premiere magazine published this series of screenplays of popular and classic movies. I was disappointed to find no information about the series on the web, so I thought I&#39;d put together what I found.
There were nineteen scripts published between 1994 and 1995.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek: Deep Space Nine Credits - All Seasons Synced</title>
      <link>https://miker.org/star-trek-deep-space-nine-credits-all-seasons-synced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 16:03:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miker.org/star-trek-deep-space-nine-credits-all-seasons-synced/</guid>
      <description>YouTube commenters have asked, so here are the combined credits for Star Trek: Deep Space Nine. Like with TNG the credits are synced around the logo.
  Deep Space Nine famously changed its theme song between seasons three and four. I&#39;ve represented this by putting the early season theme in the left channel and the later seasons&amp;rsquo; theme in the right. They don&#39;t sound too bad mixed together but this gives the option of only listening to one or the other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek: The Next Generation Credits - All Seasons Synced</title>
      <link>https://miker.org/star-trek-the-next-generation-credits-all-seasons-synced/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2021 11:44:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miker.org/star-trek-the-next-generation-credits-all-seasons-synced/</guid>
      <description>A while back I was watching a lot of episodes of Star Trek: The Next Generation. As the cast changes over the show&#39;s seven seasons, the opening credits also change and I wondered if I could sync the credits together to visualize how the changes worked.
  Finding a point to sync the videos was difficult. After trying a few different places I ended up using the moment the Enterprise first appears.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>