<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>St7565 on miker.org</title>
    <link>https://miker.org/tags/st7565/</link>
    <description>Recent content in St7565 on miker.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 02:25:42 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://miker.org/tags/st7565/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ST7565 Success</title>
      <link>https://miker.org/st7565-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2013 02:25:42 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miker.org/st7565-success/</guid>
      <description>After much screwing around, I finally got the ST7565 working with the Arduino Due. The wonderful u8glib recently added support for the Due and had preexisting support for the ST7565.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m still annoyed that I can&amp;rsquo;t get the adafruit library to work on the Due. I&amp;rsquo;m slowly porting bits of the u8glib SAM code path for the ST7565 over, but frankly I&amp;rsquo;m just annoyed with displays at this point, so I&amp;rsquo;m going to go on the something more interesting, like actually adding a clock to my alarm clock.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ST7565 and the Arduino Due</title>
      <link>https://miker.org/st7565-and-the-arduino-due/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 01:39:17 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miker.org/st7565-and-the-arduino-due/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the last several days unsuccessfully trying to get the ST7565 to work with the Arduino Due. I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to port ladyada&amp;rsquo;s ST7565 library to the SAM core without much luck.&#xA;Using the ST7565 with Uno and the library works with no issues, as would be expected, so I didn&amp;rsquo;t fuck up soldering or anything easy to diagnose like that.&#xA;Getting the code to run on the Due is not as easy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Learning to Solder</title>
      <link>https://miker.org/learning-to-solder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2013 23:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://miker.org/learning-to-solder/</guid>
      <description>One of this things I knew I need to learn to build the world&amp;rsquo;s best alarm clock was how to solder. And I was right: one of the first things I needed to do was solder wires to the ST7565 display I got from adafruit so I could hook it up to the Arduino at the heart of the clock.&#xA;Problem 1: I don&amp;rsquo;t have a soldering iron. Some quick Googling show that there are a lot of cheap soldering irons out there, and that you can probably get away with using them if you&amp;rsquo;re not doing a ton of work.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
